bitzipper.com 2016-05-08

# Bitberry Software Privacy Policy

Updated July 5, 2015

Bitberry Software is committed to protecting your privacy. You can visit most pages on our Site without giving us any information about yourself. This privacy statement explains data collection and use practices of our Sites. By accessing bitberry.com, bitberry.dk, bitzipper.com, bitzipper.dk, compressionlibs.com, finalmediaplayer.com, finaltorrent.com, finalvideodownloader.com, freefileconverter.com, freefileviewer.com, freeyoutubetomp3converter.org, photohandler.com or updatepatrol.com, (the "Sites"), you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy statement. 

### Collection of personal information

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you, e.g. when subscribing to our e-mail newsletter, or when purchasing, downloading and/or registering Bitberry Software products. The personal information we collect may include your name, company or organization name, e-mail, phone, work or home address, and credit card information.

If you purchase a license for our software or pay a voluntary donation for our free software, your personal information is transmitted to us from our ecommerce partner. This information does NOT include your credit card number or other sensitive data, only your name, email and address information. We use this information to control delivery of licensed software. 

### Collection of non-personal information

The Sites track user traffic patterns from standard web server log files. We store statistics about domain names, browser types and IP addresses. We also track search terms that are entered into search engines, but this information is not associated with individual users or IP addresses.

If you click a link inside our software products, or in the product help files, e.g. "Check for updates" or "Buy Now", you will be taken to the product Site. Information transmitted to the Site could be, but is not limited to, the language version of the product, the current day of your trial period, product version number and information about which button or link you clicked. No personal information is sent, and the information is only used for statistical purposes and to help improve our marketing screens within the product. 

### Use of personal information

The personal information collected on the Sites will be used to operate the Sites and to provide the service(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized.

We may use your personal information to provide you with important information about the product(s) that you are using, including critical updates and notifications.

The Sites may collect certain information about your visit, such as the IP address through which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the Sites; the pages that you access while at the Sites and the IP address of the web site from which you linked directly to our site. This information is used to help improve the Sites, analyze trends, and detect unauthorized downloads of licensed software.

When you sign up for our newsletter, we may use customized links or similar technologies to track e-mail links that you click. We may associate that information with your personal information in order to provide you more focused e-mail communications or purchase information. 

If Bitberry Software is acquired, our user information will be included among the assets transferred to the buyer in the sale. There also may be occasions on which Bitberry Software is required to provide information by order of a court or when the law requires that user information be treated as a transferable asset, as in bankruptcy.

### Control of personal information

Except as otherwise described in this statement, personal information you provide on the Sites will not be shared outside of Bitberry Software and affiliates without your permission.

### Security of personal information

Bitberry Software is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. However, we cannot guarantee that the information you provide to us is completely safe, although we are careful to try to prevent problems. There may be technical problems beyond our control that may make it accessible to unauthorized persons.

We never collect sensitive personal information such as a credit card number. All payment transactions are handled by trusted ecommerce partners. All information transmitted over the Internet to them, is protected and encrypted via the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. Credit card numbers are NOT stored on our servers, but are only transferred to the payment processor using a secure connection during the actual purchase. After your purchase or donation we do NOT have your credit card number.

### Use of Cookies

Cookies are small text files that most web sites, including ours, place on your computer. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

We use cookies on the Sites to store information about the site you visited us through and when you visited our Sites. This information is e.g. used to ensure that our affiliates are paid a commission for each sale that originates from their sites. For example, if you click a link to UpdatePatrol.com at www.somesite.com, we may record that you visited us through that site. If you decide to order UpdatePatrol later, we can use the cookie on your computer to recall the name of the site you visited us through.

### Protection of Children's Personal Information

Our Sites are general audience sites and do not knowingly collect any personal information from children. 

### Enforcement of this Privacy Statement

If you have questions regarding this statement, you should contact us using this form or by postal mail at Bitberry Software, Blomsterhaven 42, DK-4300 Holbaek, Denmark.
